starhub.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy | We are StarHub | StarHub

To enable us to serve you better, StarHub Ltd and its affiliates (collectively referred to herein as "StarHub", "us", "we" or "our") may, from time to time, collect or use your personal information ("Personal Information"), or disclose your Personal Information to other relevant persons. Personal Information generally refers to any information that can be used to identify you.

We may collect Personal Information about you when you sign up for our services and in the course of your using our services. Such Personal Information includes your use of our services, name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit history, geographical location and computer network and device information.

We may collect, use or disclose your Personal Information for the purposes of: planning, provisioning and billing for services, maintaining and operating our systems, managing bad debt and preventing fraud, facilitating interconnection and inter-operability between service providers, complying with any laws or rules and regulations imposed by any governmental authority, rendering assistance to any law enforcement, governmental or regulatory authority, investigating suspected or alleged breaches by you of any agreement between you and us, research, analysing customer location, preferences and demographics, supporting your customer relationship with us, facilitating any merger, acquisition or asset sale involving StarHub, or protecting StarHub and others from harm.

We may also share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information with the public and with our partners, such as our vendors, advertisers and other service providers.

We strongly believe in protecting your Personal Information. We will ensure that all reasonable security arrangements are in place to prevent any unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, copying, modification or disposal of your Personal Information. Where necessary, we will require any person to whom we provide your Personal Information to agree to comply with our Privacy Policy. While we will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that such persons comply with our Privacy Policy, we will not be liable to you if any person fails to do so.

We may revise our Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically and be kept up to date on how we protect your Personal Information.
